<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GitHub on</title><link>https://blog.villsi.net/tags/github/</link><description>Recent content in GitHub on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 02:06:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.villsi.net/tags/github/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Learn Data Science - 01 Roadmap &amp; Fundamentals</title><link>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_01/</guid><description>This Repository Consists of Free Resources needed for a person to learn Datascience from the beginning to end. This repository is divided into Four main Parts. They are:
Part 1:- [Roadmap]
Part 2:- [Free Online Courses]
Part 3:- [500 Datascience Projects]
Part 4:- [100+ Free Machine Learning Books]
This repository is a combination of different resources lying scattered all over the internet. The reason for making such an repository is to combine all the valuable resources in a sequential manner, so that it helps every beginners who are in a search of free and structured learning resource for Datascience.</description></item><item><title>Learn Data Science - 02 Statistics</title><link>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_02/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_02/</guid><description>Statistics-101 for data noobs
1 Pick a dataset Datasets repositories Generalists KAGGLE Google Medical PMC Other languages French DATAGOUV 2 Descriptive statistics Mean In probability and statistics, population mean and expected value are used synonymously to refer to one _measure of the central tendency either of a probability distribution or of the random variable characterized by that distribution.
For a data set, the terms arithmetic mean, mathematical expectation, and sometimes average are used synonymously to refer to a central value of a discrete set of numbers: specifically, the sum of the values divided by the number of values.</description></item><item><title>Learn Data Science - 03 Histograms</title><link>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_03/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_03/</guid><description>Histograms are representation of distribution of numerical data. The procedure consists of binnng the numeric values using range divisions i.e, the entire range in which the data varies is split into several fixed intervals. Count or frequency of occurences of the numbers in the range of the bins are represented.
Histograms
In python, Pandas,Matplotlib,_Seaborn can be used to create Histograms.
5 Percentiles &amp;amp; outliers Percentiles Percentiles are numberical measures in statistics, which represents how much or what percentage of data falls below a given number or instance in a numerical data distribution.</description></item><item><title>Learn Data Science - 04 ML &amp; Text Mining</title><link>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_04/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_04/</guid><description>4 Machine learning 1 What is ML ? Definition Machine Learning is part of the Artificial Intelligences study. It concerns the conception, devloppement and implementation of sophisticated methods, allowing a machine to achieve really hard tasks, nearly impossible to solve with classic algorithms.
Machine learning mostly consists of three algorithms:
Utilisation examples Computer vision Search engines Financial analysis Documents classification Music generation Robotics &amp;hellip; 2 Numerical var Variables which can take continous integer or real values.</description></item><item><title>Learn Data Science - 05 Data etc.</title><link>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_05/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_05/</guid><description>6 Data Visualization Open .R scripts in Rstudio for line-by-line execution.
See 10 Toolbox/3 R, Rstudio, Rattle for installation.
1 Data exploration in R In mathematics, the graph of a function f is the collection of all ordered pairs (x, f(x)). If the function input x is a scalar, the graph is a two-dimensional graph, and for a continuous function is a curve. If the function input x is an ordered pair (x1, x2) of real numbers, the graph is the collection of all ordered triples (x1, x2, f(x1, x2)), and for a continuous function is a surface.</description></item><item><title>Learn Data Science - 06 Free Courses</title><link>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_06/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_06/</guid><description>Artificial Intelligence CS 188 - Introduction to Artificial Intelligence, UC Berkeley - Spring 2015 6.034 Artificial Intelligence, MIT OCW CS221: Artificial Intelligence: Principles and Techniques - Autumn 2019 - Stanford University 15-780 - Graduate Artificial Intelligence, Spring 14, CMU CSE 592 Applications of Artificial Intelligence, Winter 2003 - University of Washington CS322 - Introduction to Artificial Intelligence, Winter 2012-13 - UBC (YouTube) CS 4804: Introduction to Artificial Intelligence, Fall 2016 CS 5804: Introduction to Artificial Intelligence, Spring 2015 Artificial Intelligence - IIT Kharagpur Artificial Intelligence - IIT Madras Artificial Intelligence(Prof.</description></item><item><title>Learn Data Science - 07 Project List</title><link>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_07/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/learn-data-science-for-free_07/</guid><description>500 AI Machine learning Deep learning Computer vision NLP Projects with code
This list is continuously updated. - You can take pull request and contribute.
Sr No Name Link 1 180 Machine learning Project is.gd/MLtyGk 2 12 Machine learning Object Detection is.gd/jZMP1A 3 20 NLP Project with Python is.gd/jcMvjB 4 10 Machine Learning Projects on Time Series Forecasting is.gd/dOR66m 5 20 Deep Learning Projects Solved and Explained with Python is.gd/8Cv5EP 6 20 Machine learning Project is.</description></item><item><title>Conventional Commits Guidelines</title><link>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/conventional-commits/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/conventional-commits/</guid><description>Summary The Conventional Commits specification is a lightweight convention on top of commit messages. It provides an easy set of rules for creating an explicit commit history; which makes it easier to write automated tools on top of. This convention dovetails with SemVer, by describing the features, fixes, and breaking changes made in commit messages.
The commit message should be structured as follows:
&amp;lt;type&amp;gt;[optional scope]: &amp;lt;description&amp;gt; [optional body] [optional footer(s)] The commit contains the following structural elements, to communicate intent to the consumers of your library:</description></item><item><title>计算机学习真题和仓库</title><link>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/%E8%AE%A1%E7%AE%97%E6%9C%BA%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A0%E7%9C%9F%E9%A2%98%E5%92%8C%E4%BB%93%E5%BA%93/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.villsi.net/post/2023/%E8%AE%A1%E7%AE%97%E6%9C%BA%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A0%E7%9C%9F%E9%A2%98%E5%92%8C%E4%BB%93%E5%BA%93/</guid><description>零、开始 如果是对计算机一无所知或者不确定自己是否能走编程这条道路，那么我推荐你花 10 个小时看看《计算机科学速成课》，这套课程是 Crash Course 旗下的计算机</description></item></channel></rss>